http://www.oldworldauctions.com/resources/privacy-policy

ArchiveCalendarArchiveCreate AccountLoginOld World AuctionsCurrent AuctionCreate AccountLoginSearch AuctionBrowse AuctionPast & FutureBrowse Auction ArchivesAuction CalendarInfoAuction GuideHow to ConsignFAQTerms and ConditionsClient TestimonialsMy AccountCreate AccountLoginModify Account InfoBid StatusView InvoicesConsignment StatusContact UsOpen MenuCatalog CategoriesShortcutsFeatured LotsNo Reserve LotsBuy Unsold LotsAntique Maps, Plans, Charts & GlobesWorld, Polar, Celestial, GlobesWest HemisphereNorth AmericaCanadaUnited StatesLatin America, CaribbeanAtlantic & ArcticEurope & MediterraneanAsia, Middle East, Holy LandAfricaPacific Ocean, New Zealand, AustraliaAntique Prints, Manuscripts, and Historical DocumentsTitle PagesPrintsManuscripts, Early Printing & MiscellanynewHistorical DocumentsAtlases and BooksBooks, Atlases, Travel Guides, Geography & Reference BooksAccount InfoUser InfoProfileBidding HistoryPurchase HistoryInvoicesAuction InfoBid StatusAuctionsCurrent AuctionCreate AccountLoginSearch AuctionBrowse AuctionFeatured LotsPast and FutureBrowse Auction ArchivesAuction CalendarList of Past AuctionsInfoAuction GuideHow to ConsignFAQTerms and ConditionsClient TestimonialsMY ACCOUNTAccount InfoCreate AccountLoginModify Account InfoFor BiddersBid Status & Watch ListPurchase History & Certificates of AuthenticityView InvoicesFor ConsignorsConsignment StatusConsignment HistoryView StatementsContactSend us a messagePhone and Email InfoPrivacy PolicyOverviewThis privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.oldworldauctions.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.RegistrationIn order to bid on this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address, and mailing address). If you are a successful bidder, you must provide financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.LinksThis website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 804-290-8090 or via email at info@oldworldauctions.com.About UsOld World Auctions specializes in genuine antique maps, atlases and decorative graphics originating between the 14th and 19th centuries.
Read more about us...Recent NewslettersAuction Trends in 2020Auction Trends in 2020Fake News You Won't Want to MissFake News You Won't Want to MissThe Mapmakers Who Made the 20th CenturyThe Mapmakers Who Made the 20th Century More...General InfoAbout usFAQTerms & ConditionsReferences CitedContact Info3850 Gaskins Road, Suite 220Henrico, VA 23233 (USA)Phone: 804 290 8090Email: info@oldworldauctions.com© 2018 - All Rights Reserved |Privacy Policy | Copyright Notice | Sitemap
